[
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q1.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q1.option1", "questions.shonen.q1.option2", "questions.shonen.q1.option3", "questions.shonen.q1.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q2.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q2.option1", "questions.shonen.q2.option2", "questions.shonen.q2.option3", "questions.shonen.q2.option4"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q3.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q3.option1", "questions.shonen.q3.option2", "questions.shonen.q3.option3", "questions.shonen.q3.option4"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q4.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q4.option1", "questions.shonen.q4.option2", "questions.shonen.q4.option3", "questions.shonen.q4.option4"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q5.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q5.option1", "questions.shonen.q5.option2", "questions.shonen.q5.option3", "questions.shonen.q5.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q6.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q6.option1", "questions.shonen.q6.option2", "questions.shonen.q6.option3", "questions.shonen.q6.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q7.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q7.option1", "questions.shonen.q7.option2", "questions.shonen.q7.option3", "questions.shonen.q7.option4"],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q8.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q8.option1", "questions.shonen.q8.option2", "questions.shonen.q8.option3", "questions.shonen.q8.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q9.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q9.option1", "questions.shonen.q9.option2", "questions.shonen.q9.option3", "questions.shonen.q9.option4"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q10.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q10.option1", "questions.shonen.q10.option2", "questions.shonen.q10.option3", "questions.shonen.q10.option4"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q11.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q11.option1", "questions.shonen.q11.option2", "questions.shonen.q11.option3", "questions.shonen.q11.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q12.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q12.option1", "questions.shonen.q12.option2", "questions.shonen.q12.option3", "questions.shonen.q12.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q13.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q13.option1", "questions.shonen.q13.option2", "questions.shonen.q13.option3", "questions.shonen.q13.option4"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q14.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q14.option1", "questions.shonen.q14.option2", "questions.shonen.q14.option3", "questions.shonen.q14.option4"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q15.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q15.option1", "questions.shonen.q15.option2", "questions.shonen.q15.option3", "questions.shonen.q15.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q16.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q16.option1", "questions.shonen.q16.option2", "questions.shonen.q16.option3", "questions.shonen.q16.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q17.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q17.option1", "questions.shonen.q17.option2", "questions.shonen.q17.option3", "questions.shonen.q17.option4"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.sekai.q18.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q18.option1", "questions.shonen.q18.option2", "questions.shonen.q18.option3", "questions.shonen.q18.option4"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q19.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q19.option1", "questions.shonen.q19.option2", "questions.shonen.q19.option3", "questions.shonen.q19.option4"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "questions.shonen.q20.question",
    "options": ["questions.shonen.q20.option1", "questions.shonen.q20.option2", "questions.shonen.q20.option3", "questions.shonen.q20.option4"],
    "correct": 0
  }
]
